<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connect, Command &amp; Control IoT devices on Eclipse Hono&amp;trade;</title>
    <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Connect, Command &amp; Control IoT devices on Eclipse Hono&amp;trade;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://eclipse.dev/hono/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artifacts for installing and using Hono</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/downloads/</guid>
      <description>Binaries Eclipse Hono&amp;rsquo;s service components are provided by means of pre-built Docker images available from Docker Hub. These container images can be deployed to popular container orchestration platforms like Kubernetes and OpenShift.&#xA;The Eclipse IoT Packages project hosts the Hono Helm chart which can be used to install the most recent release of Hono to a Kubernetes cluster using the Helm package manager. Please refer to the deployment guide for installation instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Hono without installing locally</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/sandbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/sandbox/</guid>
      <description>We are providing a publicly accessible Eclipse Hono™ sandbox environment at hono.eclipseprojects.io. The main purpose of the system is to provide an environment for experimenting with devices and how to connect them to Hono without the need for setting up a local instance.&#xA;Accessing the Sandbox The sandbox hosts a Hono instance consisting of the components listed in the table below. The components can be accessed as described in the Getting started Guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get involved in the Hono Project</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/contributing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you for considering to contribute to Eclipse Hono™. We really appreciate the time and effort you want to&#xA;spend helping to improve things around here. And help we can use :-)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Additional Resources covering Hono</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/presentations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On this page you can find links to arbitrary resources covering Eclipse Hono™ which have been presented at events, conferences&#xA;and meet-ups or are available online.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get in touch with the Hono Community</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/get-in-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/get-in-touch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wanna tell us what you think about Eclipse Hono™? What we can improve? Which feature is missing? Or just discuss&#xA;architectural issues?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of past and future Hono Releases</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/road-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/road-map/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are trying our best to anticipate the needs and requirements of users based on the feedback we get from users. From this&#xA;information we create and maintain &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eclipse-hono/hono/projects?type=classic&#34;&gt;Project Boards&lt;/a&gt; on GitHub&#xA;for upcoming Hono versions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hono Load Tests with CoAP devices</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/blog-load-tests-coap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/blog-load-tests-coap/</guid>
      <description>This page is presenting load tests of an Eclipse Hono deployment with simulated CoAP client devices. It shows how the system is configured and what load it could handle.&#xA;Components The setup consists of following components.&#xA;Kubernetes The Kubernetes is AWS EKS cluster using 3 x c5a.large machines.&#xA;Hono Hono is deployed using Eclipse IoT Packages helm chart, version 2.6.0.&#xA;Specific helm values:&#xA;# Configuration properties for protocol adapters. adapters: # kafkaMessagingSpec contains the configuration used by all protocol # adapters for connecting to the Kafka cluster to be used for messaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizations supporting the Development of Hono</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/community/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>YourKit is kindly supporting this open source project with its full-featured Java Profiler. YourKit, LLC is the creator of innovative and intelligent tools for profiling Java and .NET applications. Take a look at YourKit&amp;rsquo;s leading software products: YourKit Java Profiler and YourKit .NET Profiler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is new &amp; noteworthy in Hono?</title>
      <link>https://eclipse.dev/hono/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse.dev/hono/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>2.7.0 New Features The duration after which cached metrics, which are maintained by protocol adapters for adhering to messaging limits, are being refreshed, can now be adjusted as a fixed fraction of the overall cache timeout duration. This allows fine tuning of the adapters&#39; behavior with regard to accepting/rejecting messages from devices of tenants for which the message limits are being exceeded. Please refer to the Admin Guide for details.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
